

ANDREY SAMAEV

WEB DEVELOPER VUE/LARAVEL

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

years of practice Web Development. JavaScript and JS Framework VUE JS working proficiency. Good expertise HTML/CSS stack, preprocessors. Ready to continue with React. Keen for highquality and focus on best user experience. Quickly and communicate with people.

MY EXPERTISE

- Typescript, JavaScript (ES2015 2019)
- Vue, Laravel, Vuex, React, Redux
- HTML5, CSS3, Sass (SCSS), BEM, Bootstrap, Bulma
- Fetch, REST API, Web sockets, SQL
- Basic of Photoshop, Laravel
- Git/Github, VS Code, WebStorm, Chrome Developer Tools (incl. React), NPM, Webpack
- Algorithms: Solved 60+ katas on CodeWars, 5KYU
- Basic OOP understanding
- English: Upper Intermediate

EDUCATION

EAST UKRAINIAN NATIONAL UNIVERSITY Master degree with honor on engineering

HOW TO CONTACT ME

+38 0500 222 777
Telegram: @SamaevJS
andreysamaev@gmail.com
Linkedin: Andrey Samaev
Github.com/Samaev
Skype: a.samaev
Kyiv, Ukraine
Ready to work remotely

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer VueJS|Laravel { Core IT Development, Fin Tech }
October 2023 - present

 Working on Vue/Laravel 2 projects -fin tech and online shop.

Frontend Developer VueJS|Laravel { Hubspot HealthCare(USA)}
August 2022 - october 2023

- Working on Vue/Laravel/Hubspot project (complex CMR sytem) with English speaking team in Frontend Developing.
- Obtaining tasks with SQL, PHP Laravel so easy for me).

Frontend developer, SearchInform.com March, 2020 - February, 2022

Technologies: JavaScript, React, Typescript, HTML, CSS, BEM

See some of my projects at:

-Landing page for MyBIKE (React) <u>Demo</u>

<u>GitHub Code</u>

- -Landing page for Museum NAMU Demo GitHub Code
- ToDOAPP React <u>DEMO</u>

GitHUB Code

- -<u>Currency converter (Angular) Demo</u> <u>GitHUB Code</u>
- -<u>TIC TAC TOE game (Angular) DEMO</u>
 GitHub Code
- JavaScript Expertise:
- Proficient in JavaScript language fundamentals and concepts.
- Comfortable with asynchronous programming and promises.
- Skilled in building dynamic and interactive user interfaces.